<resources>

    <string name="app_version">1.2.1</string>
    <string name="app_name">FHD &amp; 4K Wallpapers</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Home</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">For you</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Pro Picks</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">Popular</string>
    <string name="tab_text_5">Most Downloaded</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_image">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="tabs_header">Set Tabs</string>
    <string name="notification_header">Notifications</string>
    <string name="large_text">
    "Developer and owner of this App is Sayantan Biswas,\n\n"

        "Sayantan is a School Student who is currently reading at School and in class 12"
        "he has made this app for providing the best performance and value to the users"
        "that are currently watching for the best wallpaper app and I am so glad that it"
        "successfully completed and it is available for you. \n\n"

        "So, everyone knows that how much hard App making is but, because"
        "Sayantan is not a good developer but still he knows coding much and he made this app successfully. \n\n"

        "Sayantan Tried to make this App much interactive and good looking, hope you liked"
        "this app if you have any queries related to this app, any feedback or any queries"
        "then you can reach Sayantan out through a message on Instagram. Sayantan will definitely make"
        "those changes as soon as possible if it is a valid issue or any security flaw.\n\n"

       "He lives in India in West Bengal state at a small city called Cooch Behar, he has only a"
        "computer from which he made this app, Sayantan has written good algorithms to make this app"
        "useful to you, if you have any query related to this then definitely Sayantan should know through"
        "a message on Instagram.\n\n"

        "You can Follow Sayantan to the social accounts that are provided to get all the updates for other useful apps published by him.\n\n"

        "Your Sincerely Sayantan"
    </string>

</resources>